tattoofinder.com 2011-01-03

# About TattooFinder.com

The Internet contains a wealth of information; unfortunately, it may also contain personal details about you that you don't want everyone to know. For example, your real name (lots of people on the Internet use aliases, alter egos, or nicknames), street address, phone number, or e-mail address. When you go online, sites you visit may be gathering information about you without your knowledge. At TattooFinder.com, we strive to help our customers protect their privacy while using our services.

TattooFinder.com's policy is to respect and protect the privacy of our users. This policy statement tells you how we collect information from you and how we use it. Using the Internet should be a fun experience and we want to help you make it so. Be assured that TattooFinder.com will not disclose your personal information to third parties without your consent. TattooFinder.com may disclose user information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) TattooFinder.com's rights or property, other TattooFinder.com users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. TattooFinder.com may disclose user information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it. TattooFinder.com shares aggregate information about our users with advertisers, business partners, sponsors, and other third parties. For example, we will say TattooFinder.com's audience is x percent female and y percent male. This data is used to customize TattooFinder.com's content and advertising to deliver a better experience for our users. There are cases where TattooFinder.com may ask you for personal information such as your name, e-mail address, and birth date. For example, we request personal information when you make a purchase with TattooFinder.com. TattooFinder.com needs to collect this information for fulfilling prizes, tracking/verifying compliance with TattooFinder.com policies as well as federal, state, and local laws, and/or for editorial and feedback solicitation purposes. In case you change your mind or some personal information changes (such as your ZIP code), we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update, or remove the personal data you give us.

**POLICIES FOR KIDS (INDIVIDUALS UNDER 13 YEARS OF AGE)**

TattooFinder.com encourages parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate in the activities offered on the sites. No information should be submitted to or posted at TattooFinder.com by Guests under 13 years of age without the consent of their parent or guardian. Unless otherwise disclosed during collection, TattooFinder.com does not provide any personally identifying information, regardless of its source, to any third party for any purpose whatsoever from our Guests under 13 years of age. All registrants receive an e-mail confirming their Registration. In addition, when a Guest under 13 registers, he/she is required to provide the e-mail address of his/her parent or guardian and that parent or guardian receives an e-mail alerting them to that Registration. Although Guests under 13 years of age may be allowed to participate in some contests and promotions, if such a Guest wins, notification and prizes are sent to the parent or guardian identified in the initial registration process. Publication of names, ages, or images for contest winners under 13 require parental or guardian consent.

**POLICIES FOR TEENS (INDIVIDUALS 13 TO 17 YEARS OF AGE)**

Teens are required to provide the e-mail address of a parent or guardian and a notification message is sent to the parent or guardian of all Guests who are 13 to 17 years of age, which identifies the information supplied at Registration and allows the parent or guardian to be aware of and participate in the Guest's online experience.

**USE OF IP ADDRESSES**

An IP address is a number that's automatically assigned to your computer whenever you're surfing the Web. Web servers -- the big computers that "serve up" Web pages -- automatically identify your computer by its IP address. TattooFinder.com collects IP addresses for the purposes of system administration, to report aggregate information to our advertisers, and to audit the use of our site. When Guests request pages from TattooFinder.com, our servers log the Guests' IP addresses. We do not normally link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable, which means that a user's session will be logged, but the user remains anonymous to us. We can and will use IP addresses to identify a user when we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our rules or terms of service or to protect our service, site, customers, or others. Some services within TattooFinder.com, such as certain message boards, may display IP addresses along with the message poster's name and message. Please review each service prior to use and only use those that disclose information you are comfortable with sharing.

**USE OF COOKIES**

What are cookies? Cookies are pieces of information that a Web site transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies make Web-surfing easier for you by saving your preferences while you're at our site. We never credit card information in cookies. The use of cookies is an industry standard -- you'll find them at most major Web sites. By showing how and when Guests use a site, cookies help us see which areas are popular and which are not. Many improvements and updates to the site are based on such data as total number of visitors and pages viewed. This information is most easily tracked with cookies. We use the information from cookies to provide services better tailored to our users needs. Visitors to TattooFinder.com always have the option of disabling cookies via their browser preferences. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, note that some parts of the TattooFinder.com service will not function properly or may be considerably slower if you refuse cookies.

**LINKS TO OTHER SITES**

Users should be aware that when they are on TattooFinder.com, they could be directed to other sites that are beyond our control. There are links to other sites from TattooFinder.com pages that take you outside our service. For example, if you "click" on a banner advertisement, the "click" takes you off the TattooFinder.com site. This includes links from advertisers, sponsors, and partners that may use TattooFinder.com's logo as part of a co-branding agreement. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. Please keep in mind that whenever you give out personal information online --- for example, via message boards or chat --- that information can be collected and used by people you don't know. While TattooFinder.com strives to protect their users' personal information and privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online and you do so at your own risk. TattooFinder.com's policy does not extend to anything that is inherent in the operation of the  
Internet, and therefore beyond TattooFinder.com's control, and is not to be applied in any manner contrary to applicable law or governmental regulation.

**THIRD-PARTY ADVERTISING**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use some of the above discussed information (not including your name, address, email address, payment information, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](https://www.google.com/adsense/support/bin/answer.py?answer=94149).

**SECURITY**

The importance of security for all personally identifiable information associated with our Guests is of utmost concern to us. We exercise great care in providing secure transmission of your information from your PC to our servers. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, TattooFinder.com can't ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. When credit card information is transmitted we use industry standard, SSL (secure socket layer) encryption. TattooFinder.com will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or e-mail. Ultimately, you are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and any account information.

**YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THESE TERMS**

By using this site, you signify your assent to the TattooFinder.com Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our site. Your continued use of the TattooFinder.com site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this Web site's privacy statement, you should first contact the company as follows: TattooFinder.com, 1115 Broadway, Denver CO 80203; telephone number: (303) 774-0208; or via e-mail.

**TattooFinder.com's INTERNET SAFETY TIPS**

  * Keep your passwords private, even from your best friend! Your online service will never ask for them, so neither should anyone else.
  * Use only your member name and/or e-mail address when chatting or sending e-mail.
  * Never give out personal information like your name, address, or phone number.
  * Don't share photos of yourself, your family, or your home with people you meet online.
  * Always delete unknown e-mail attachments without opening them. They can contain destructive viruses. 
  * If a person writes something that is mean or makes you feel uncomfortable, don't respond. Just log off and tell your parents, who can report it to your online service provider.
  * Remember that nothing you write on the Web is completely private \-- including e-mail. So be careful and think about what you type and who you tell. Not everyone is as nice, cute, and funny as they may sound online.   
Never make plans to meet an online "friend" in person.
  * WHEN IN DOUBT -- always ask your parents for help -- and just LOG OFF if you're not sure! You can always go back online later.
